Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Hello?
Hey.
- Stay away
from me! Stay away from me!
How many
of you can hear me?
Why is everyone quiet
all of a sudden?
How many of you are there?
I'm here.
Look, I'm not
here to hurt anyone, okay?
Okay, I just woke up here.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm just trying to
figure this out, okay?
Okay.
I don't know where I am either.
What's the last
thing you remember?
I don't know.
My head hurts.
Me too, just try to remember.
I was home.
Then the last thing I remember.
I'm freezing.
It's okay.
I'm wearing a jacket.
I'll give it to you.
Follow the sound
of my voice, okay?
Okay.
Can you walk?
I'm coming toward you.
- I can't see
Okay, I'm coming to you.
Sorry.
That's my hand.
At least I found you.
There's two of us.
I'm giving you my
jacket, put it on.
I heard at least two
other voices before.
Where are you?
Hello?
- Please don't leave me.
Where are
you, say something.
Anyone remember anything?
Anyone see a light or anything?
I just woke up here in darkness.
Just keep talking
so I can find you.
Don't leave me.
I'm scared, please.
- What the hell?
- Where are we?
Can anyone hear me?
- Whoa.
- Hey, give me that.
- And why would I
want to do that?
Fine, take it.
What's wrong with him?
- I don't know, maybe
something they drugged us with.
You're okay.
What?
Just calm down.
We all just woke up here too.
We're not gonna hurt you.
- Stay back.
- Just take it easy, man.
- Hey!
Let me out of here!
- Hey, are you okay?
Are you pregnant?
- Yeah.
- I already tried that.
- Hey, she's fucking pregnant.
- Someone give her their weapon.
Give her your machete.
- Wait a minute.
Give that pregnant
lady your machete.
Why?
Because a girl with
a gun told you to.
Give it to her, I'm not
going to say it again.
- Okay, okay.
I'm not the enemy here.
Thank you.
Just everybody watch where
they point those things.
- Come on.
Hey, somebody
let me out of here!
- Please, please stop, please.
- Hey man, knock it off!
- Just calm down.
- Hey!
Man, knock it off! Why
don't you come over here?
- I see.
You found the tools.
Good.
But tools are nothing
until you learn how to use them.
- Where are we?
Why are we here?
To find out who we
really are, Sean.
Wait, how do you know my name?
- I know a lot about you.
And I want to know
more about all of you.
- Oh god, this is
too fucking crazy.
I gotta get out of here,
gotta get fucking out of here.
Somebody let me out of here!
- Richard, pay attention.
I am going to tell you
how you can get out.
Okay, I'm listening.
My name is Dr. Kasuma,
and this is my experiment.
On this screen, you will
see a person who is trapped.
You can free that person
very easily and yourself.
All you have to do is
kill someone in this room.
- That's crazy.
- Tracey, what is your maternal
instinct telling you to do?
My instinct is telling
me that you're sick
and I don't want to
play your little game.
That's fine.
But I guarantee someone
else will play eventually.
None of us are gonna decide
to kill someone in this room.
- No?
You are all strangers.
But this woman, she
is someone one of you
will miss very, very much.
- Sarah, Sarah.
She is safe for now,
but not for long.
Are you willing to do what
it takes to free your wife
and yourself, Richard?
Olivia, you have
tools in your hand.
You can free yourself and you
can leave anytime you want.
Please, I don't want to
be here anymore, please!
- No, no, no, no, Olivia,
begging does you no good.
First person to kill
someone here leaves.
By killing first, you'll
save your own life
and that of someone else.
You can walk right out the door
but you have to
earn that privilege.
Alice, I see you found
a very powerful tool.
I hope you use it wisely.
You have until the
timer goes off to
decide if this woman lives or
dies, save her and yourself.
- Sarah, talk to
me, where are you?
Can you hear my voice?
Kill someone and we live.
Why?
I mean, how can we
even believe her?
- You will believe me, L,
because you have
no other choice.
When the timer runs out
the lights will go out
and one of you must die.
- Just calm down, man.
You're not making any sense.
Just relax and calm down
while we try to think.
- You just want me
to fucking relax?
You want me to relax?
They have my wife's
somewhere in a cell,
and you want me to relax?
- Oh God, Sarah.
Your wife is okay, Richard.
My wife is okay.
Oh, is she?
She's okay?
All good.
Good, that's good.
That's good.
You think she's okay?
Fuck you!
- Do you recognize that
woman in the screen?
I've never seen that woman.
- I think she's trying to say is
are you in on this whole thing?
What do you know?
Are you part of that
lady's experiment?
I've never seen that woman.
- Look, you two look
an awful lot alike.
Am I suppose to think that's
a fucking coincidence?
- It's not that much
of a coincidence.
there is a whole fucking,
- That's too much of
a coincidence for me!
- Look, Olivia is in here
with all of us, okay?
How could she be in on it?
Something's not right
about her being here.
- Nothing is right
about any of this.
We have to try to get out of
here any way that we can, okay?
Let's try prying the door
open with your hatchet.
- Richard, we could use your ax.
Richard, please, come on.
- Stay the fuck away from me.
You should cover your
ears in there little one.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- Can you hear me, anything?
- Gimme that gun, we
gotta shoot the lock off!
No way, this gun is mine.
Get your own.
- I'm not playing, give
me that fucking gun.
- Fuck you.
What part of gun beats knife
and every other weapon in this
room don't you understand?
- Come on, you don't have
to take the gun from her.
She can shoot the
lock off herself.
Alice, right?
Look, I'm unarmed.
If we can get this door open,
we can all get out alive.
Why do you keep acting
like you know everything?
We have no idea what's on
the other side of that door.
The only thing I know
for certain right now is
if I keep this gun,
I'm going to live.
I'm tired of your shit.
Do not make me take
that gun from you.
Go ahead.
You'll take a bullet
to the face too.
We don't have much time left.
What are you gonna do?
What is he going to do?
I'm not gonna do anything.
I'm not..
I'm not gonna kill anybody.
I bet you'd think different
if you had the gun.
Gun, ax, hatchet, I'm
not a fucking killer.
None of us deserve
to die right now
this is all just ridiculous.
Even to save her life?
Fucking pussy.
You
don't fucking know me.
Stay back!
- You don't know me.
None of you fucking know me.
None of you know me!
So you'd rather kill any
of us? Murder is that easy?
Hey, this is all still
just hypothetical, right?
- Till the timer runs out
and the lights go out...
- This all could
be a game, right?
I mean, she keeps calling
this an experiment
like it's a psychological test.
I mean, there's no way that
she expects any one of us
to kill somebody in this room.
This is real.
There's nothing
hypothetical about it.
- Hey, are you okay?
- Yeah, please just
stay away from me.
- What do you expect
me to do then, huh?
What do you want me to do?
Hack one of these
people to death
In order for my wife to live?
Is that what you want?
What do you want from me?
Let me talk to my wife.
Let me talk to my wife!
Richard?
Sarah, Sarah, Sarah,
can you hear me?
Who's there with you?
Are you alone?
Are they feeding you?
Where are you?
I'm real close.
I know things haven't
been good in a long time
and I'm sorry, I know
I pushed you away,
and I just, if you
can get me out of here
I'll be so much better,
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm so sorry.
- Just don't worry,
okay, just relax.
We're gonna get you out of there
and then we're gonna go home.
- Okay, I can't wait.
Oh God, Richard, I love you.
Let me talk to my wife.
Let me fucking talk to my wife!
Let me talk to my wife!
If my wife dies, I'm not a
killer, I didn't do this,
I'm not, this isn't
me, I didn't kill her.
It's that fucked up woman
on TV, she's the killer.
She's the one that's
doing this, not me.
I didn't do this.
Somebody do something.
Stop the fucking ticking!
Somebody let me out
of here, please!
Somebody please
help me out of here!
No!
- Was that you screaming?
Are you alright?
Yeah, I didn't mean to scream.
I thought he was
coming toward me.
- I didn't do it, are you happy?
Did you get your results?
Good, write them down.
Your experiment worked.
I'm not a killer, you got that?
Now open the door
and let us out.
Richard, you love your wife.
And she obviously loves
you very much too.
But you didn't love her
enough to save her, did you?
You know the
consequences of inaction.
But seeing is believing.
Richard, Richard,
please help me.
No, no, no, Sarah,
Sarah, Sarah, no.
What is that?
- Richard, please help me!
Richard, where are you, help me!
Richard, I can't breathe.
Sarah, focus.
Sarah, focus, there's gotta
be a way out of there, okay?
There's gotta be a
way out of there,
just look around, look around,
pound the walls, scream.
Is there a window, a door?
Look over there.
Look, look, look, behind you.
- Hello, Richard, help me.
Oh God, Sarah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Richard,
but I don't like the
results of this experiment.
But tell me, why didn't you
do anything to save your wife?
I didn't do it, I didn't do it.
- They say you don't know
what you have until it's gone.
Do you know what you
had now, Richard?
- Okay, that's enough.
Richard, your wife isn't dead.
This is just another
part of their experiment.
And they just gassed her
the same way they did us
when they brought us here
Your wife is fine.
- No Sean, his wife
is indeed dead.
I can provide more graphic
proof if you don't believe me.
- That's enough, stop torturing
us and let us out of here.
- This isn't torture,
this is a test.
Would you like me to show
you the difference, L?
- This isn't a test.
This is sadism, you freak.
Please, please, just
let us go, please.
There's one way out
of here for you.
Follow the rules
of the experiment.
- Crazy bitch has my sister!
- Whoa, whoa, calm down, watch
where you point that thing.
Why, I might kill someone?
Have you fuckers been
paying attention?
They're going to kill my sister
if I don't kill one of you.
The only question now is which
one of you deserves to die?
You?
Don't you point that
fucking thing at me.
You?
Or him?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We don't know if anybody
is actually dead yet.
- You're right.
That's actually possible.
The gas, maybe they just knocked
her out for a little while
the same way they did us.
No, she's gone.
She's gone.
I saw her face.
Oh, it's my fault.
No, it's not your fault.
She knew that you loved her
and you were there
for her when she died.
What does it matter?
We're not growing old together.
We're not having a family.
She's dead. Period.
The end.
That's it.
You stay away from me.
Just leave me alone, okay?
- Just put it away, there
has to be another solution.
- Look at him.
Ask him and his wife if
there's another solution.
- Alice, put the gun
down, you're not a killer.
I'm not.
No! You're not a killer!
Fuck you, you don't
know anything about me
and I don't know
anything about you.
Why would I choose
any of your lives
over the life of my sister?
Just hold on a second, okay?
Look, you've got a gun and
there's still time left.
Let's just take a second
and talk things out, okay?
- Fine, talk!
Just stay back.
Okay, so what?
- What, I'm supposed to
have all the answers?
I just want us to talk before
things get out of control.
- Things are already
out of control.
Alright, so what do we know?
That lady can see
us and hear us.
So any escape attempt
that we might try to do.
- Look, there's no
way they could get us
in this room by themself.
There's gotta be more
people outside that door.
I can't hear anything.
I can't hear anyone out here.
She knows.
Me?
Tell us, how many of your
friends are out there?
- I already told you,
I was forced into
this room same as you,
I have nothing to do with this.
- Maybe you do, maybe you don't,
I know the fastest
way to find out.
Stop it, alright,
we have to work together if
we want to get out of here.
- Wait, wait, if they had his
wife and they have your sister
it makes sense that
they have someone
that each of us cares about.
- Tracey's right.
They got us and our loved ones.
So, so where, where are
they keeping them, huh?
Here?
In the same building
or somewhere else?
Just no way of knowing.
- We don't even know
where we are right now.
What does it all mean?
I mean, what does that doctor
lady, what does she want?
You know what she wants,
she wants me to kill
someone in this room!
- And if this is an experiment,
there has to be
a way to beat it.
- They tell us that they
want us to kill someone
but that can't be the answer.
They must be looking
for something.
What are they trying to find?
- They want to see
us act like animals!
They're using people we
love to manipulate us.
If I kill one person, I
get out of here alive.
My sister gets out too,
now that sounds like a
way better deal to me
than dying in here with
a bunch of strangers.
Hey, just wait a minute.
This isn't about love.
That doctor lady, she's
playing us like rats.
She wants to see us fight.
Yeah, and I'm about
to end this game.
Should have killed one of you,
I could've been
with her right now.
You couldn't kill for your wife.
That doesn't mean
you're a bad person.
- No, it just means I'm weak.
Come on, go ahead, go
ahead, shoot me, come on.
Stay back.
- Go on, shoot me.
Come on, come on, do it.
- Stay back.
Shoot me, I'm volunteering.
Save your sister.
Save your sister, save yourself.
Get out of here and end this.
- Richard, you don't
mean that, don't do it.
You don't have to do this.
Do you want to see her
dead in front of you?
Just do it.
- Don't do it.
- Do it.
- Hurry!
Let him go, Alice. -Stop!
Just do it, shoot,
shoot, come on.
Do it, come on, do it, I'm
volunteering, just shoot me.
Natalie?
Come on, pull the
fucking trigger.
Do it, do it now.
Come on, you can do it.
Pull the motherfucking trigger.
Are you fucking kidding me?!
- Look at you now.
You don't have shit,
just like the rest of us.
You're stuck here.
And your sister's gonna die.
Fucking die!
- No, no, help me, help me!
I don't wanna die,
please help me!
Please help me.
- You stabbed her!
No, no, I just took the
machete, I needed a weapon!
You did this.
- I didn't do it, he did it.
- I didn't touch her!
Then why are you bleeding?
- You tell me, I wasn't
the one that touched her.
- Come on guys, help her!
Alice, please, you
have to save her.
You have to save my baby.
Please help me.
- Alice, you better
fucking help her.
Please, anybody help me.
- We can't, it's either
her or my sister,
I can't, she's gotta die.
Get away from her!
Alice, I know
you're a good person
and I don't blame you for this.
I don't blame you, but your
sister's gonna be fine.
But my baby.
Tracey, your baby is dead!
- No, no, no, not yet.
No, just help me.
Please just help me!
- Please, she needs a doctor,
she's fucking pregnant!
Come on, have some decency!
Alice, I trust you, I trust you.
I need you to save her.
What's her name?
- I don't know, we were waiting
until she was born to name her.
But, um
um maybe Rose.
Help her.
Alice, Alice, you
can't let her die.
You can do anything
what you want.
Wait
- Okay, okay, what can I do?
- You need the smallest,
sharpest weapon in here.
- Where's the knife, where's
the knife, give it to me.
Shit, you just had it.
- Then do it for her!
- Give her your knife.
Just give it to her, man.
- Give her your fucking knife!
Now what?
- Okay, okay, you're going to
have to listen to me because
once you start, I'm not
going be able to help you.
You're going to have
to cut horizontally
across my pelvis and then
you're gonna to have
to pull her out.
How will I know where to cut?
- I have a scar from my son.
I'm gonna do it, okay?
- Okay, okay.
- I'll take care of her, okay?
I'm gonna make sure she's okay!
No one's gonna touch her.
- Okay, I trust
you, I trust you.
- I'm gonna reach in to
get the baby out, okay?
Is she okay?
- She's fine.
Hold your baby girl.
So we fix our eyes
not on what is seen,
but on what is unseen,
for what is seen is temporary,
but what is unseen is eternal
That was a
nice effort, Alice.
Too bad, you couldn't
save Tracey's baby
or your poor sister.
- What?
The kill needs to happen
before the lights come on.
I didn't do this,
but she's dead.
That's not right.
This is all an experiment.
There's no right or
wrong here, Alice.
I only want to learn
from the best result.
Alice, can you hear me?
Please, I'm scared.
Alice, come and get
me out of here, Alice.
You're still gonna kill
her sister after all this?
By failing to
follow instructions,
all of you killed her sister.
You're a monster.
You are the monster,
Sean. Don't you see?
You all are.
My experiment is
only proving that.
And the result from
this experiment
will change the way we
all think about humanity,
morality, life, love
and of course, death.
You can't turn me
into a murderer.
She's dead, please, she's gone.
Please just spare my sister.
You gave me fucking blanks.
I'm trying to kill!
Your excuses are
unacceptable, Alice.
Natalie, can you hear me?
I can't help you.
I can't help either of us.
I'm so sorry.
You know me, I can't
do anything right.
- It's okay, Allie,
I know you're good.
I know you've been
looking out for me.
You've always been so
much stronger than me.
- I'm not strong, I was selfish.
I've always been selfish.
I'm sorry I wasn't a
better sister to you.
I'm sorry I stole
everything from you.
I stole your boyfriends,
your money, everything.
I tried to save you.
I really did.
- I'm just tired.
I'm just gonna go to sleep.
No, Natalie, don't go to sleep.
Natalie, can you hear me?
You evil bitch!
You're going to kill
all of us, aren't you?
I'm not the one making
the choices here, you are.
- Do you think it stopped?
Do you think that
means that she's seen enough?
A person like that
never sees enough.
- Maybe she wants to
see what happens next.
How we deal with this trauma.
- There's no way we're all
getting out of here alive.
- This is an experiment, right?
Maybe she got the
results she wanted.
I mean, they saw
Richard not do anything.
They made Alice attempt to
kill and Tracey getting hurt.
It was just an accident.
She knows I didn't do anything.
She just wanted to
see my wife die.
She would do
anything for anybody.
I can still see her face
just coming towards me.
It's just happening over
and over and over again.
It's like I'm fucking
living in hell.
I was ready to shoot that
poor man in the face.
- Come on, let us out,
haven't you seen enough!
- The doors aren't opening,
nothing's happening.
- That door isn't going to open.
Then what's this waiting for?
- The bitch is crazy.
Maybe she just wants to
see us all kill each other.
- Look the TV's off.
There's no ticking.
Maybe she's thinking it over.
- You think she's
planning on letting us go?
We should come up
with a plan too.
Hey, stay back we're
not out of anything!
Okay, okay, no problem.
Please, open the door!
- The door, open it?
You think they're
gonna open that door?
They're never gonna
open that door.
They are never
opening that door,
we're all gonna die in here.
We're all gonna die
and rot in this room.
Open the door!
I don't wanna die
in here, please!
I just wanna go back home alive.
We just wanna go back home.
We don't care what you want.
We don't care!
Please let us go
back home alive!
- Come on!
Let us out!
The experiment isn't over yet.
It is absolutely essential
that you continue.
- Who is that?
Who knows her?
I know her.
She's my girlfriend.
Ana, can you hear me?
Ana?
Ana, Ana, hey, hey,
can you hear me?
Look, look, I'm
here, I'm here, Ana.
- Hurry, help, I love you.
I don't know how
I got here, baby.
I don't know what's happening.
Baby, just be patient,
okay, just be patient.
I will get you out, okay, I
promise, I promise to you, okay?
- I love you.
I love you too.
I don't want to have
to kill you, Richard.
But I'm going to have to.
- I know, I know, I know.
I understand.
I'm done, done playing.
Just do it.
- I think you have to
make it easy for me.
I think you should
kill yourself.
You allowed your wife to die
because you couldn't
kill for her.
Now it's time.
This is really sharp.
You can slit your wrist
with it very easily.
Let me show you.
Slice your wrist down
your arm like this.
Not across.
You will bleed out
really quickly.
It will barely hurt.
- Seriously, you're
gonna let this happen?
- Shut up!
I can't watch this.
- This is my fucking
business, okay?
- Richard, you don't
have to do this.
- Hey, it's his call, man.
- Make her do it,
she should do it.
- Shut up!
- I can do this.
I can do this, let me do this.
She should be here.
She shouldn't be dead.
- She shouldn't be dead.
- No.
- But she is now, join her.
Yes.
- Yeah.
- You can kiss her.
- Yeah, so do it.
Oh.
Shh.
- Oh fuck.
Now look at me, look at me.
You'll be with her soon.
Go to sleep.
Sleep, Richard.
Thank you, Richard.
This is fucked up.
This is all so fucked.
I tried to kill
him just like her.
She's gonna kill us
all anyway, isn't she?
No, she isn't.
We just have to figure it out.
Hey L?
- Yeah.
- Back there with Tracey,
what were you saying?
What do you mean?
- Sounded like scripture.
How did you know all that?
- Oh, that's, my Mom used to
take me to church every Sunday.
Do you still go?
- No, I stopped
going when I was 12.
It's weird though, I
still remember, you know.
- What does it all mean?
- I think it just means
whatever you go through in life.
It's all just temporary.
It'll all pass.
Sorry, Olivia, suicide
isn't the same as murder.
You're doing well though,
learning the darker
side of human nature.
You're almost there, but
if you want to escape
you can't just let a
person take their life.
You must take it from them.
When do you think that she's
going to make her move?
She'll probably
wait till it's dark.
Someone's going to die
when the lights go off.
She's the one that
stabbed Tracey.
Yeah, I think so too.
- I can hear everything
you're saying, you know.
This room is not very large.
You should know that by now.
- And you're right,
I killed her.
I thought she was you, Alice.
- Someone is going to die
when the lights go out.
But right now I'm still alive.
And so is the only
woman that I ever loved,
and I intend to do
whatever I have to do
to make sure that she
isn't going to die.
Olivia, it's not worth it.
Give yourself up to me, Sean.
I'm willing to have
sex with you first
if that's what you want.
I will be gentle
afterwards, I promise.
- Olivia, you're not
thinking clearly.
- Yes, I am.
Everything is very
clear right now.
Clearer than it has
ever been, really.
Olivia, we should all talk.
- I'm tired of talking, Sean.
Come on, there has to be
another way out of here.
Look, we can use your
hatchet and my ax
and we can chop
through the wall.
We can still get out of here.
And go where, Sean?
Go where?
You don't know what's
on the other side.
There's no way out of
here except one way.
No.
You're not a killer, Sean.
Look at you.
Holding that ax.
Olivia, just stop.
I'm not gonna fight you.
Good, surrender to me.
- Olivia, please, don't do it.
Look, I'm gonna drop my weapon.
You have said too much.
You will never be the same.
- Olivia!
I'm sorry I had to be
the one to push you
into becoming who
you really are.
If any of us is
pushed far enough
there's no telling what
we will do to survive,
so don't feel guilty.
This is all my fault.
- I don't feel guilty.
I just know I did everything
I could to stay alive
and you did everything you could
to drive that poor girl crazy.
- And yet, Sean, you
surprised me today.
I thought you would give in
to such a beautiful
girl like Olivia.
I'm surprised you could
resist such a beautiful woman.
What are you saying?
- I know everything
about you, Sean.
I know how you
brought another woman
into your bed when
your wife was away.
Where is my wife?
Do you have my wife?
Of course not.
Why would I take your wife
when clearly you don't care much
about whether she's hurt or not?
But, I have a person
that you really love.
- Jacob, oh my God, Jacob.
Jacob, are you okay?
Where's my boy?
- And L, you are not so
innocent either, are you?
The difference between
you and Sean is
you hurt the person
you love the most.
Remember, when you ran away
and you broke her heart?
- What are you talking about?
Mom?
Leonard?
Mom, where are you?
Don't worry about me.
Are you hurt?
You know your Mama,
nothing can really hurt me.
Mama, I was gonna
come back home.
I'm gonna come get you.
I'm still gonna come back.
Final test, decide who
lives and who dies.
This is fucked up.
This is so fucked up.
We're all just gonna
end up dead like them.
I mean, for all we
know they're forcing us
to kill each other but
my sister could be alive.
I'm sorry, Alice, but
your sister's dead.
I'm not gonna let
her kill my son.
- Even if my sister's dead
killing each other
isn't worth it.
We're all acting like animals
slaughtering each other.
She's right.
The doctor's not
even in here, man.
We're the ones getting
our hands dirty.
She hasn't laid a
finger on anyone.
Fucking Tracey,
she was pregnant.
She would have done
anything for her baby.
Sean, I know you would have
done anything for your child.
And L, I know your Mom
would do anything for you.
That doesn't mean that
we should keep playing.
When the timer goes off,
the lights are gonna go out
and she's going to want
for us to kill each other.
We're not going anywhere.
Might as well just stop.
Richard was right.
Richard was the only
one who was right.
He died with dignity.
He didn't kill anyone.
Didn't even try.
- You know she's right, Sean.
I'm not gonna kill you.
That's not what my Mom
would want anyways.
It's a dark road and I'm
not going down it, man.
- I don't want to
kill you either,
but my son, they got my son.
And I can't let him die.
My son is eight.
He hasn't had a
chance at life yet.
I'm sorry, but I
gotta take you down.
If there's even a chance of
saving him, I need to win.
I'll get you.
You walk around smiling,
acting all in charge,
acting like you're a good guy
till nobody's looking, man.
Yeah, I'm not that
great of a guy, okay.
But that little
boy there, he is.
He got cancer when he was six.
We were told that he
only had six months.
His mother and I,
we fought for him.
But you know what?
Our relationship got to
the point where she left
and I met someone to
help me take my mind away
if just for a moment.
I made a mistake and
I'm still sorry for it.
- Well, congratulations.
I'm a fuck up, okay?
I admit it, but my son,
he's better than I am.
I'm not going to let
some crazy lady kill him.
You all may not think
that I'm a survivor
but you know what, my son is.
And I'm not gonna let him die.
Yeah, we'll see when
the lights go off.
- What about me, Sean?
If you kill L, does that mean
you're going to kill me too?
You lost your sister.
You should do what Richard did
and take yourself out of this.
- You know what I said before
about how we shouldn't
play anymore?
I've changed my mind.
- What?
- I've changed my mind.
I want to kill you, Sean,
if it's the last thing I do.
Watch it, Alice.
Watch it, you stay out of this.
- No, I'm in this
more now than ever
and I'm ready for you, Sean.
- You don't get it, man.
You know how much anger it takes
for people like us to survive?
Man, you think 'cause
you killed some girl
that was chasing after
you with an ax first,
you can understand what
it takes to survive, man?
You don't know shit!
Every day of my life has
been about survival for me
and the people that I love.
Today isn't any different for me
just because I'm
stuck here, man.
Today's just another day,
just another day
where I don't know
if me or anybody
else that I love
is gonna make it
through tomorrow.
So welcome to my world, Sean.
This is what's always
like for me, man.
- You really think that you
can beat me with that knife?
Hey L, Sean's right about me.
I've got nothing
left to live for,
but I'm still angry.
That's still there.
And I don't want to
see you win, Sean,
even if it means I die.
You want to know why?
I just don't like you.
That's not fair,
Alice, that's not fucking fair.
- Shut up, people
like you always win.
- It's not fair, that's
not fucking fair.
It ain't Alice you
gotta worry about, Sean.
- Come on, L.
Okay, I'm not a killer.
I'm just a dad, okay?
I just want to save my kid.
Please, just let me win.
- Where are you going, Sean?
Kill him, L!
- I will.
- Come on!
- No, no I can't!
No, no!
- Get off me!
Alice!
Thank you for helping me, Alice.
- No Sean, don't do this.
You tried to kill me.
- I didn't touch you.
Yeah, but you gave him a
machete so he could kill me.
No! Seriously,
stop Sean, please.
We're past that, Alice.
I'm not gonna debate
this with you.
What about your son?
What kind of example
are you setting?
- My son is dead!
Choked, lifeless,
but you know what?
We're all survivors, right?
Is that right, huh?
All of us!
You, L, Richard, Olivia, Tracey,
we're all survivors!
You know what, it's
just that some of us
are better at it than others.
Yeah, but you don't
have to kill me,
you don't have to do this.
We can still get out of here.
I'm done talking to you, Alice.
Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up, L.
- Please stop!
Sean!
Shh, shh, come on, Alice!
Alice!
Alice.
You fucking bitch.
I'd rather be a
bitch than a corpse.
What are you doing?
Don't you have any decency?
- I do Alice, I do,
but not everyone has the luxury.
You must conclude the test.
You have no other choice.
You must go on.
- Just do it.
Just do it, just leave.
- No, I'm going to get
you out of here, okay?
I'm going to get you out.
- Alice, you gotta leave.
- No, I'm going to get
you out of here, okay?
Don't worry, I'm
gonna get you out.
You're gonna carry me
right out that door?
- Yeah, yeah.
Alice you gotta do this,
you gotta end this.
- Alice, you gotta leave.
Just do it, alright?
- No.
I won't leave you,
I won't leave you.
- I will soon.
- No, no, no.
Please, L. Stay with me.
- There is a dark side
to obedience, Alice.
Thank you for showing me.
I have learned more
than I ever wanted to.
Fuck you!
- Alice, you have
no other choice.
You must kill him.
You have made it this far.
You have to end it.
Please embrace the
animal inside you.
You must continue.
- I'm not going to,
I'm not going to.
Then you will die together.
- Alice, Alice?
- No, no, no, no.
Look at me, Alice, look at me.
You have to do this
to save yourself, ok?
- Kill me.
Do it.
- Just close your eyes.
Go to sleep.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
No, no!
No, let me out of here!
No!
waited for you
call the choirs
made of love